<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hatsvali on Mestia Hotel Level by Malkhaz &amp; Nata Paliani</title><link>https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/tags/hatsvali/</link><description>Recent content in hatsvali on Mestia Hotel Level by Malkhaz &amp; Nata Paliani</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 12:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/tags/hatsvali/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>9-day winter tour example</title><link>https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/blog/winter_week_tour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/blog/winter_week_tour/</guid><description>An example of a 9-day ski tour to Svaneti. The tour can be called an extreme holiday, but beginner skiers (snowboarders) will be happy too.
Season from December to March
Plan 1 (Sat) Arrival in Tbilisi. Excursion program; — Check-in at a hotel in Tbilisi. 2 (Sun) Transfer Tbilisi-Mestia. — Stop for lunch along the way; — Check-in at the Shgedi hotel.
3 (Mon) Skating! Hatsvali resort
— Beginners study with instructors; — Experienced people ride on their own; — Evening program.</description></item><item><title>Hatsvali and Tetnuldi skiing</title><link>https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/blog/winter_skiing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://malkhazpaliani.github.io/blog/winter_skiing/</guid><description>Two ski resorts, Hatsvali and Tetnuldi, are waiting for you. Beginners will enjoy the modern ski lifts and spacious pistes, while experienced skiers will appreciate the challenging freeride options with a vertical drop of 1000 meters.
Hatsvali From the hotel window you can see the ski slopes. The ride to the cable car takes 10 minutes.
Height 1865 - 2347 meters Height difference: 482 meters Number of tracks: 3 The length of the green, simplest route is 700 m; The length of the blue (longest) route is 2,600 m; The length of the red track is 1,900 m; Lift with cabin.</description></item></channel></rss>